Does work ever leave you feeling stuck in a rut with limited opportunities to be creative?
工作是否曾让你感到陷入一成不变的常规，创造力机会有限？
To thrive, you might want to increase your brain's flexibility.
要想脱颖而出，你可能需要增加大脑的灵活性。
But is this even possible, and if so, how?
但这可能吗？如果可能，又该如何做呢？
Most jobs require the ability to problem-solve and cope with challenges, at least to a certain extent.
大多数工作需要解决问题和应对挑战的能力，至少在某种程度上。
Imagine a teacher who has a new and very nervous student in their class.
想象下一位老师，班上来了一个非常紧张的新学生。
If that teacher is a flexible thinker, they will be able to adapt their classroom management, even if they haven't seen this situation before.
如果这位老师是一位思维灵活的人，即使之前没遇到过这种情况，他们也能够调整他们的课堂管理方式。
According to Leonard Mlodinow, author of Elastic, flexible thinkers rely on idea generation and imagination – they are willing to experiment and take risks.
《弹性思维》一书的作者伦纳德·莫洛迪诺夫认为，思维灵活的人依赖于产生创意和想象力——他们愿意尝试和冒险。"
"Elastic thinking is what you need when the circumstances change, and you are dealing with something new.
当情况发生变化，你面对新事物时，你需要的就是弹性思维。
It's not about following rules."
这与遵守规则无关。"
Therefore, instead of following the typical procedure for inducting a new student, the teacher might come up with a tailored response, based on prediction and previous experience.
因此，教师可能不会遵循接纳新生的典型程序，而是基于预测和以往经验提出量身定制的应对方法。
So, how can you become a more flexible thinker?
那么，你如何成为一个更灵活的思考者呢？
According to Dr Lisa Feldman Barrett, it's all about exercising the brain.
丽莎·费尔德曼·巴雷特博士说，关键在于锻炼大脑。
One way of doing this, she says, is through exposure to a variety of experiences which make it easier to adjust to new situations.
她说，方法之一是通过接触各种各样的经历，这让你更容易适应新情况。
A lot of companies now consider flexible thinking in the workplace, especially when it comes to design.
许多公司现在考虑工作场所的灵活思维，尤其是在设计方面。
Workspaces may have couches where workers can lie down and relax, giving them the space to come up with and process new ideas.
工作空间可能有长沙发，员工可以躺下放松，给他们空间来产生和处理新的想法。
Mlodinow says it's very important to take time to daydream, listen to ideas and concepts you disagree with and spend time doing activities outside of your comfort zone.
莫洛迪诺夫说，花时间做白日梦，倾听你不同意的想法和概念，花时间做舒适区以外的活动，这些都是非常重要的。
This will help you understand multiple points of view and therefore blossom in many different aspects of your career.
这将帮助你理解多种观点，从而在你职业生涯的许多不同方面成长和发展。
So, if you want to make a change, you can become a flexible thinker too, with a little practice.
所以，如果你想做出改变，通过一点练习，你也可以成为一个灵活的思考者。